Guide to the United Federation of Teachers Photographs PHOTOS 019
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: New York Teacher Photograph Files, 1951-1987.
  - Subseries I:U: Miscellaneous.
    - Educational Forum, Jun 1970 (Item 1142)
    - School Service Officers Meeting, Dec 1970 (Item 1295)
    - Drugs? Let's Find Out [WNYE-TV, Brooklyn, television program], 1971 (Item 1413)
    - Sesame Street Cast, Jan 1971 (Item 1524)
    - Junior High School, Representatives Meeting, Jan 7, 1971 (Item 1354)
    - District School Board Principal's Institute, Penn-Garden Hotel, Jan 9, 1971 (Item 1294)
    - Soccer Team Naming Contest Winners [New York Cosmos], Feb 1971 (Item 1480)
    - Brussels Conference, Brussels, Begium, Mar 1971 (Item 1415)
    - HS Equivalency Course Regisration, Gramercy Park Hotel, Jun 1971 (Item 1753)
    - East New York, Brownsville section, scenes of bad conditions, Sep 1971 (Item 1956)
    - Africa, Black and White Map, Oct 1971 (Item 1599)
    - Sickle Cell Anemia Program [St. Mary's Hospital, NY], Dec 3, 1971 (Item 1841)
    - HIP Consultative Councils, Spring 1972 (Item 1870)
    - Corning Flood Photo, CTA studies pact enforcement, 1972 (Item 2082)
    - Corning Flood, 1972 (Item 2082)
    - Ocean Hill-Brownsville Redevelopment Program/Signing of Agreement, May 8, 1972 (Item 807)
    - NYCT Tarrytown Meeting, first meeting of new organization leaders, 8/26-28/72, Aug 26, 1972 (Item 1913)
    - Van Dyke, George, First TWX Message at Albany, Sep 1972 (Item 2140)
    - SPS 31 "Boy Scouts Meeting", Dec 1972 (Item 2240)
    - Human Relations Council Meeting, Feb 1973 (Item 2221)
    - JHS Programming Course, Feb 1973 (Item 2622)
    - Recruitment and Training Program, Annual Staff Conference, Apr 1973 (Item 2335)
    - UTNR Conference Day, Apr 1973 (Item 2621)
    - Education Development Council members, North Rockland, Jun 1973 (Item 344)
    - Labor Theater, Jun 3, 1973 (Item 2563)
    - Joyear Members, Anna Klein, Charlotte Schier Selector, Sarah Berenson, Nov 1973 (Item 2744)
    - Highway Safety Meeting, Nov 1973 (Item 2754)
    - Berlin, Memorial Sign of Nazi Oppression, Nov 1973 (Item 2758)
    - HS Institute, on collective bargaining, Dec 1973 (Item 2808)
    - New York Labor and Government Leaders, 1974 (Item 3127)
    - Mental Health Workers Election, Jan 1974 (Item 2925)
    - Mental Health Workers, Jan 1974 (Item 2957)
    - College Bound Coalition, Feb 1974 (Item 2880)
    - West African Famine, drought, Feb 1974 (Item 2888)
    - Peru Summer Camp Program, Feb 1974 (Item 2918)
    - Build Teacher Power [written in blocks], Mar 1974 (Item 2895)
    - State Aid Meeting, Mar 1974 (Item 2903)
    - Shop Steward Registration, Mar 1974 (Item 2920)
    - Higher Education Conference, Mar 1974 (Item 2951)
    - Saterlee Trailer, Apr 1974 (Item 2967)
    - Elk Grove, Saterlee Trailer, Apr 1974 (Item 2969)
    - ECEA Legislative Luncheon, Apr 1974 (Item 2979)
    - State Aid Meeting, Apr 1974 (Item 2982)
    - Kansas City, strike, Apr 1974 (Item 2991)
    - JHS Programming Course, Apr 1974 (Item 3002)
    - Rochester Board of Directors Meeting, May 1974 (Item 3034)
    - National Labor Relations Act, Jul 1974 (Item 3218)
    - Staten Island "Learn In", Sep 1974 (Item 3263)
    - Fire Fighters Convention Delegates, Sep 1974 (Item 3289)
    - Women Trade Unionists, Sep 1974 (Item 3364)
    - White House Fellows, Oct 1974 (Item 3328)
    - White House Fellows meet with Al Shanker, Nov 1974 (Item 3503)
    - Higher Education Conference, Dec 1974 (Item 3476)
    - Delegate Assembly, 1975 (Item 4049)
    - Wheelers' House in Elmira, Jan 1975 (Item 3433)
    - United Nations Drug Abuse Conference, Jan 1975 (Item 3511)
    - New York Hilton, Lady Hilton Room, Jan 1975 (Item 3532)
    - CAN/ACT, Cortland County, Jan 1975 (Item 3537)
    - The Old Bourbon Steak House, Feb 1975 (Item 3534)
    - Where We Stand, Little Rock, Boston: Same Thing, Feb 9, 1975 (Item 3448)
    - Hands, Mar 1975 (Item 3615)
    - 'Pinocchio' Bill Baird's Musical version, Mar 1975 (Item 3646)
    - Laser Beam Checkout System, May 1975 (Item 3668)
    - National Commission for Observance of International Women's Year, May 1975 (Item 3747)
    - Italian-American Guidance Institute, May 1975 (Item 3751)
    - Coalition Meeting, Gramercy Park Hotel, Jun 1975 (Item 3769)
    - Black Educators for Israel's Survival, Nov 1975 (Item 3888)
    - Coaching Course, Dec 1975 (Item 3948)
    - Singing Boys of LI, Dec 1975 (Item 4032)
    - Summer Career Guidance Institute, 1976 (Item 4576)
    - Labor Management Conference [Atlanta, GA, Coretta Scott King with Steelworkers President I.W. Abel], Feb 1976 (Item 4000)
    - Human Events, taping course, Philadelphia, Feb 1976 (Item 4161)
    - Teachers for Children Fund, Mar 28, 1976 (Item 4471)
    - Labor Coalition, Plattsburgh, Apr 1976 (Item 4093)
    - "I Paid My Dues" a Labor Musical, Apr 1976 (Item 4159)
    - NYC All Union Musical Show, Apr 1976 (Item 4304)
    - Italian-American gymnastic meet, May 1976 (Item 4237)
    - Plattsburgh, NY, SUEP [?] Elects new officers, May 1976 (Item 4239)
    - Gymnastics Fantastics, May 1976 (Item 4414)
    - Bell Telephone System, May 30, 1976 (Item 4475)
    - How Children See Our World [Child's drawing], Jun 6, 1976 (Item 4433)
    - Teachers Education Conference, Harold Robinson, Antonia Cortese, and Helen Grune, Oct 1976 (Item 4638)
    - George Meany Center for Labor Studies, Silver Springs, Maryland, opening, Nov 1976 (Item 4693)
    - South Bronx, 1978 (Item 4856)
    - Classroom Discipline Conference, 1979 (Item 5201)
    - Health Professionals, Bellvue Hospital Organizing Campaign, 1979 (Item 5203)
    - Educational TV, Public Television [Includes but may not be limited to:] Edelman, Howard, 1979 (Item 5224)
    - Higher Education, Collective Bargaining Conference, Apr 1979 (Item 4198)
    - Picnic in the Park, Jun 1979 (Item 5204)
    - Higher Education, Conference on Academic Unionists, Oct 1979 (Item 4198)
    - Pascack Valley Hospital Strike, Oct 1979 (Item 5203)
    - Citywide Holocaust Conference, Nov 1979 (Item 4833)
    - Higher Education, Irwin Polishook, Sanders, Deedy, and Koenig, 1980 (Item 4198)
    - Municipal Nurses Collective Bargaining Filing, Jan 14, 1980 (Item 5203)
    - Democratic Caucus Voting, NYS Democratic Primary Caucus, Apr 1980 (Item 5264)
    - Human Association Courses, May 1980 (Item 5057)
    - Democratic Caucus Voting, Democratic National Convention [Includes but may not be limited to:] Taitt, Ann; Burns, Robert; Rustin, Bayard; Knapp, Frances; Feldman, Sandra; Mitchell, Peter; Sorkin, Neal, Aug 1980 (Item 5264)
    - Health Professionals, Registered Nurses Victory, Oct 1980 (Item 5203)
    - School Improvement Plan Meeting, Nov 1980 (Item 5227)
    - NYS Coach of the Year 1980-81, Steve Jackowski, 1981 (Item 5386)
    - School Improvement Plan Meeting, Mar 1981 (Item 5227)
    - School Improvement Plan Meeting, Apr 28, 1981 (Item 5227)
    - Open Doors Economic Council, Jun 1981 (Item 5486)
    - School Improvement Plan Meeting, Kaufman, Barbara and Stills, Fred, Aug 1981 (Item 5227)
    - Heimlich Maneuver poster, Aug 1981 (Item 5489)
    - Labor Theater, Chuck Portz in "Jack London," one-man show, Oct 1981 (Item 2563)
    - School Improvement Plan Meeting, Oct 1981 (Item 5227)
    - White House Conference on Aging, State Delegates Meeting, Oct 1981 (Item 5473)
    - White House Conference on Aging, Delegation with Kenneth Deedy, Nov 1981 (Item 5473)
    - Referendum Count, 1982 (Item 5561)
    - Women Trade Unionists, Film, "With Babies and Banners" promo shot, Feb 1982 (Item 3364)
    - School Improvement Plan Meeting, Jun 1982 (Item 5227)
    - Labor Coalition, Bargaining, Aug 1982 (Item 4093)
    - NY Knicks Promo, Nov 21, 1982 (Item 5580)
    - New York Knicks, 1984 (Item 5601)
    - UTPA Anniversary, 1984 (Item 5637)
    - Statue of Liberty Celebration, Jun 1984 (Item 5593)
    - Ethiopia, 1985 (Item 5642)
    - NYC Marathon, 1985 (Item 5751)
    - CED Press Conference, Sep 1985 (Item 5740)
    - NBC Program, "To be a teacher", Jan 5, 1987 (Item 5781)
    - International Affairs Conference, undated (Item 128)
    - Holiday Hills, undated (Item 133)
    - White House Conference on Education, undated (Item 160)
    - Peace Corps in India, undated (Item 164)
    - Computer Institute ad photos, undated (Item 169)
    - First bi-monthly check, undated (Item 170)
    - Needlework Photos, undated (Item 170)
    - Lamp of Learning, undated (Item 172)
    - Needlework photos, undated (Item 185)
    - Easter Charter Flight ad photo, undated (Item 185)
    - [Reproduction of] B. Krigstein's "1865: The War Is Over", undated (Item 185)
    - Operation Soapbox, What Makes Education News, Textbooks in our schools, analyzing the MES program, secretaries in the schools, reconstructing education, industrial revolution in education, undated (Item 185)
    - Board Committee to reduce paperwork, undated (Item 188)
    - Implications of Federal Aid, the community role in education, assessing UFT, partnership of teachers and counselors, undated (Item 188)
    - Equality in education, undated (Item 195)
    - Needlework photos, undated (Item 195)
    - Towards a federal school system, undated (Item 196)
    - Members of Community Education Problems Committee, undated (Item 200)
    - Travel Photographs, undated (Item 208)
    - Child Care, Camps, Foster Care, Abuse, Care, Working, undated (Item 214)
    - Medical Care Blood Center, undated (Item 215)
    - Aged, Rehabilitation and Recreation, undated (Item 216)
    - [Art, various photographs of paintings, sculptures, and other works of art], undated (Item 222)
    - Nigerian Play photos, undated (Item 249)
    - Saturday Evening Post cartoon, undated (Item 249)
    - "Hey, They're After Us!" cartoon, undated (Item 249)
    - State Supreme Court House, undated (Item 250)
    - Needlework photo, undated (Item 251)
    - Needlework Photos, undated (Item 321)
    - Children in school, Oma Riggs article, undated (Item 329)
    - Madison Square Garden Marquee, undated (Item 335)
    - Coffee urn, undated (Item 393)
    - "Zeely" Book Cover, undated (Item 408)
    - Co-Op City, undated (Item 415)
    - HIP Drawings for Junior Art Contest, undated (Item 425)
    - Hospital Workers Strike, undated (Item 447)
    - Supreme Court Building, Washington DC, undated (Item 459)
    - APA Repertory Company, undated (Item 474)
    - Hippie Fashions shown in 5/15 "United Teacher", undated (Item 533)
    - Red Cross photos, undated (Item 536)
    - National Conference of Paraprofessionals, undated (Item 612)
    - "EH" Play, undated (Item 690)
    - Hudson Vitamin Inc. discussions, undated (Item 721)
    - Detroit Ratification Meeting, undated (Item 742)
    - Adirondack Road, undated (Item 789)
    - Bridge from Covington, Kentucky to Cincinnati, Ohio, undated (Item 1030)
    - Cartoons, undated (Item 1033)
    - Hunter, Doris, showing paycheck to Al Shanker, undated (Item 1038)
    - Arden House, Artwork, undated (Item 1163)
    - Big Bird, Sesame Street, undated (Item 1217)
    - NYS Capitol Building, Albany, NY, undated (Item 1297)
    - Congregational Church Brooklyn. Committee candidates, undated (Item 1381)
    - United Nations, undated (Item 1385)
    - Theatre Review Pictures, undated (Item 1500)
    - Performing Arts Pictures, undated (Item 1881)
    - Cartoon, The Odd Couple [NEA and SCME's Wurf cutting last zero off of a wedding cake labeled "2,000,000 Teachers"], undated (Item 1920)
    - Turner, Frances, parent, representing the Advisory Council, meets with functional group for in depth examination of function, undated (Item 1940)
    - Education Conference Board presentation to regents, undated (Item 2691)
    - State Aid Meetings, undated (Item 2884)
    - "L'Chaim--To Life!" Film, undated (Item 3492)
    - Hilton, 'Le Grill' Restaurant, undated (Item 3553)
    - Postage Stamp, undated (Item 3687)
    - Pollution, undated (Item 4083)
    - Higher Education - LaValle, Kenneth (Senator); Siegel, Mark; Wakshull, Sam; Westchester Community College; Kennedy, Edward M., undated (Item 4198CR)
    - The Spirit of 76 Fife and Drum Corps, undated (Item 4345)
    - The Age of Jackson [illustration of President Andrew Jackson], undated (Item 4476)
    - Manpower, undated (Item 4766)
    - Albany Skyline, undated (Item 4922)
    - Urban Community Insurance Company, undated (Item 4930)
    - Lake Placid, Olympic Games, Michael Luce, undated (Item 4986)
    - Arts in Curriculum Council, undated (Item 4991)
    - Newspaper Art, undated (Item 5010)
    - Free Materials Art, undated (Item 5010)
    - Wheeler, Colin, Book Art, undated (Item 5010)
    - Book Review Art, undated (Item 5010)
    - Ethnic Studies, undated (Item 5010)
    - Film, With Babies and Banners, undated (Item 5011)
    - Mummenshanz Mimes, undated (Item 5057)
    - Jean Cocteau Repertory Production, undated (Item 5057)
    - Miscellaneous - groups of people - public figures - celebrities - kids, etc., undated (Item 5057)
    - Clements, undated (Item 5057)
    - Celebrities, undated (Item 5057)
    - Kids Are People, undated (Item 5057)
    - "Scared Straight," Film, undated (Item 5112)
    - Pins and Needles, undated (Item 5118)
    - Board of Examiners 80th Anniversary, undated (Item 5172)
    - Norma Rae (film), Sally Field with Norma Rae, undated (Item 5187)
    - Norma Rae (film), Shots from movie, undated (Item 5187)
    - Norma Rae (film), Students from Norman Thomas HS view movie, undated (Item 5187)
    - Hudson River Psychiatric Center, undated (Item 5203)
    - PULSE (Nurse Organizing Publication) with Contacts, undated (Item 5203)
    - Solar Energy, Carol Burkhart, undated (Item 5214)
    - Solar Energy, undated (Item 5214)
    - Project ACE [Includes but may not be limited to:] Kessler, Ann; Impellizzeri, Irene; Aiello, Stephen, undated (Item 5215)
    - [Unidentified people seated around table, holding up glasses], undated (Item 5263)
    - Soup Line Protest, Cincinnati, Against Reagan Budget Cuts, undated (Item 5390)
    - Labor Education Advisory Services, PSC at, with Dorothy Shields (AFL-CIO), undated (Item 5434)
    - Wald, Lillian profile taken during training NY Hospital, Founder of the Nurses' Settlement, NYC, undated (Item 5506)
    - Prisoners of Conscience, undated (Item 5572)
    - Taylor Institute, undated (Item 5589)
    - Replicas of flag, undated (Item 5594)
    - Odyssey, undated (Item 5600)
    - Education Evaluators, undated (Item 5612)
    - Metropolitan Life Breakfast, undated (Item 5644)
    - Computer, undated (Item 5648)
    - Kennedy Airport, gates, undated (Item 5663)
    - [Unidentified event], undated (Item 5722)
    - GHI, undated (Item 5742)
    - Educational Evaluators, undated (Item 5744)
    - KCC, undated (Item 5745)
    - Polish Family Board Meeting, undated (Item 5747)
    - Mexican Earthquake, undated (Item 5752)
    - Essay Contest, undated (Item 5754)
    - Historical, undated (Item 5758)
    - Immigrants, undated (Item 5759)
    - Space Shuttle, undated (Item 5769)
    - Arden House, undated (Item 5783)
    - Israel Trip Brunch Reunion, undated (Item 5786)
    - Task Force, undated (Item 5805)
    - Evander, undated (Item 5806)
- Series II: United Federation of Teachers General Photograph Files, 1960-1980.
  - BOTC Mini Grant, 1991-1992 (Box Shared Tamiment 018, Folder 5-8)
  - Chandler, Porter, R. (Chair, Board of Higher Education), 1968 (Box 26, Folder 421)
  - Chavez, Cesar at UFT - Frontlash sponsored high school press conference, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 422)
  - Demonstrations, 1968 (Box Shared Tamiment 018, Folder 9)
  - Farber, Barry (portrait), undated (Box 26, Folder 423)
  - Federation of Catholic Teachers, undated (Box 26, Folder 424)
  - Historical - Queens elementary school classroom, with students and teachers. (John D. Lorenzo - husband of Jeanette DiLorenzo - is one of the students pictured.), 1910-1919 (Box 26, Folder 425)
  - Individuals - Unidentified, undated (Box 26, Folder 426)
  - Labor Council for Latin American Advancement, undated (Box 26, Folder 427)
  - McLoughlin, Randall Scott, undated (Box 26, Folder 428)
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 26, Folder 429, Box Shared Tamiment 017, Folder 11)
  - New York City Community School Board Candidates and Members, 1970-1979 (Box 26, Folder 430)
  - New York City Marathon (UFT members participating) - Undated. (Box 26, Folder 431)
  - New York State United Teachers (NYSUT) - Demonstrations, undated (Box 26, Folder 432)
  - New York State United Teachers (NYSUT) - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 26, Folder 433)
  - O'Reilly, Peter (Fr.), undated (Box 26, Folder 434)
  - Retirees Association of District Council 37, undated (Box 26, Folder 435)
  - Rustin, Bayard - Portraits, undated (Box 26, Folder 436)
  - Shanker, Edith, undated (Box 26, Folder 437)
  - UFT - Contracts and Negotiations, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 438)
  - UFT - Demonstrations, 1960-1989 (Box 26, Folder 439)
  - UFT - High School Coaches, undated (Box 26, Folder 440)
  - UFT - Hines, George, South Bronx Attendance Teacher, undated (Box 26, Folder 441)
  - UFT - Italian-American Study Committee, 1984-1990 (Box 26, Folder 442)
  - UFT - Labor Day, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 443)
  - UFT - Manhattan Borough Office, undated (Box 26, Folder 444)
  - UFT - Officers - Altomare, George, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 445)
  - UFT - Officers - Altomare, George, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 446)
  - UFT - Officers - Altomare, George, 1960-1969 (Box 26, Folder 447)
  - UFT - Officers - Altomare, George, 1960-1969 (Box 26, Folder 448)
  - UFT - Officers - Altomare, George, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 449)
  - UFT - Officers - Altomare, George, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 450)
  - UFT - Officers - Altomare, George, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 451)
  - UFT - Officers - Altomare, George, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 452)
  - UFT - Officers - Altomare, George, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 453)
  - UFT - Officers - Altomare, George, 1970-1979 (Box 26, Folder 454)
  - UFT - Officers - Altomare, George, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 455)
  - UFT - Officers - Altomare, George, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 456)
  - UFT - Officers - Altomare, George, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 457)
  - UFT - Officers - Altomare, George, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 458)
  - UFT - Officers - Altomare, George, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 459)
  - UFT - Officers - Altomare, George, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 460)
  - UFT - Officers - Altomare, George, 1980-1989 (Box 26, Folder 461)
  - UFT - Officers - Altomare, George, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 462)
  - UFT - Officers - Altomare, George - United Steelworkers/Phelps Dodge, undated (Box 26, Folder 463)
  - UFT - Officers - Cogan, Charles, undated (Box 26, Folder 464)
  - UFT - Officers - Espaillat, Edwin, 1976-1989 (Box 27, Folder 465)
  - UFT - Officers - Feldman, Sandra, undated (Box 27, Folder 466)
  - UFT - Officers - Harris, Sidney (Party honoring Sidney Harris [UFT Assistant Secretary, 1965-1978] at home of Jeanette DiLorenzo, Staten Island, NY), 1980 (Box 27, Folder 467)
  - UFT - Officers - Kolodny, Jules, undated (Box 27, Folder 468)
  - UFT - Officers - Koury, Fred, undated (Box 27, Folder 469)
  - UFT - Officers - Lefkowitz, Abraham, undated (Box 27, Folder 470)
  - UFT - Officers - Marsh, Alice, undated (Box 27, Folder 471)
  - UFT - Officers - Portalatin, Maria (Portraits and conference photos), 1978-1986 (Box 27, Folder 472)
  - UFT - Officers - Shanker, Albert, 1960-1969 (Box 27, Folder 474)
  - UFT - Officers - Shanker, Albert, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 475)
  - UFT - Officers - Shanker, Albert, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 476)
  - UFT - Officers - Shanker, Albert, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 477)
  - UFT - Officers - Shanker, Albert, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 478)
  - UFT - Officers - Shanker, Albert, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 479)
  - UFT - Officers - Shanker, Albert - Portraits, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 480)
  - UFT - Officers - Shanker, Albert, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 481)
  - UFT - Officers - Shanker, Albert, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 482)
  - UFT - Officers - Shanker, Albert, 1977 (Box 27, Folder 483)
  - UFT - Officers - Shanker, Albert, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 484)
  - UFT - Officers - Shanker, Albert, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 485)
  - UFT - Officers - Shanker, Albert, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 486)
  - UFT - Officers - Shanker, Albert, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 487)
  - UFT - Officers - Shanker, Albert, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 488)
  - UFT - Officers - Shanker, Albert - Portraits - Undated (Box 27, Folder 489, Box Shared Tamiment 017, Folder 11)
  - UFT - Officers - Shanker, Albert with others - Undated (Box 27, Folder 490)
  - UFT - Officers - Shapiro, Morris - Portraits and with others, 1970-1979 (Box 27, Folder 490)
  - UFT - Officers - Simonson, Rebecca, undated (Box 27, Folder 492)
  - UFT - Officers - Weingarten, Randi, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 493)
  - UFT - Officers - Group photos with other labor union leaders, undated (Box 27, Folder 495)
  - UFT - Scholarship Selection Committee, undated (Box 27, Folder 496)
  - UFT - Schools and Students - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 27, Folder 497)
  - UFT - Spring Conference, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 498)
  - UFT - Spring Conference, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 499)
  - UFT - Spring Conference (High School of Art and Design students at UFT Spring Conference), 1975 (Box 27, Folder 500)
  - UFT - Spring Conference (Rustin, Hobart and others speaking.), 1975 (Box 27, Folder 501)
  - UFT - Spring Conference, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 502)
  - UFT - Spring Conferences, Undated (Prints, Negatives, Contact Sheet) (Box 27, Folder 503)
  - UFT - Staff (Color slides), 1988-1989 (Box 27, Folder 504)
  - UFT - Staff? Undated (Box 27, Folder 505)
  - UFT - Strikes, 1960s, 1960-1969 (Box 27, Folder 506)
  - UFT - Taylor Act passage, Albany, NY - Snapshots, Mar 1969 (Box 27, Folder 507)
  - UFT - Unidentified Meeting, Jun 1970 (Box 27, Folder 508)
  - UFT - Voting, undated (Box 27, Folder 509)
  - Zonarich, Nicholas, undated (Box 27, Folder 510)
  - UFT Officers--Selden, David, 1960-1971 (Box 28, Folder 531)
- Series III: Predecessor Unions, 1928-1961.
  - Subseries III:A: Teachers' Union Auxiliary
    - Teachers' Union Auxiliary - Conferences at Hudson Guild Farm, Netcong, New Jersey, 1928-1929 (Box 25, Folder 422)
  - Subseries III:B: Teachers' Union
    - Teachers' Union, 1940 (Box 28, Folder 512)
    - Teachers' Union, 1942 (Box 28, Folder 513)
    - Teachers' Union, 1943 (Box 28, Folder 514)
    - Teachers' Union, 1944 (Box 28, Folder 515)
    - Teachers' Union, 1945 (Box 28, Folder 516)
    - Teachers' Union, 1946 (Box 28, Folder 517)
    - Teachers' Union, 1947 (Box 28, Folder 518)
    - Teachers' Union, 1948 (Box 28, Folder 519)
    - Teachers' Union, 1949 (Box 28, Folder 520)
    - Teachers' Union, 1940-1949 (Box 28, Folder 521)
    - Teachers' Union, 1950 (Box 28, Folder 522)
    - Teachers' Union, 1951 (Box 28, Folder 523)
    - Teachers' Union, 1952 (Box 28, Folder 524)
    - Teachers' Union, 1953 (Box 28, Folder 525)
    - Teachers' Union, 1955 (Box 28, Folder 526)
    - Teachers' Union, 1950-1959 (Box 28, Folder 527)
    - Teachers' Union, 1961 (Box 28, Folder 528)
    - Teachers' Union, 1960-1969 (Box 28, Folder 529)
  - Subseries III:C: Teachers' Guild
    - Teachers' Guild - Leaders, Activists, Events (incl. reception luncheon(?) for Johnna Lindlof [seperated from Wagner 22]), 1943 (Box 28, Folder 530)
    - UFT-Officers-Selden, David, 1960-1971 (Box 28, Folder 531)